

DYLAN HENDRIX

- ✓ dylanhendrix6@gmail.com
- **J** 0615454510
- ☆ Oldengaarde, 2, 5655CR Eindhoven
- # June 1, 2006
- dylanhendrix.github.io/Portfolio2024
- in linkedin.com/in/dylan-hendrix-bnbhu

SKILLS HTML CSS JavaScript C# Unity UI/UX LANGUAGES Dutch English

PROFILE

I am an intermidiate **Software Developer** from **the Netherlands** specialized in **web and game development**. Proficient in diverse platforms and languages. Familiar with multiple development tools and techniques. Capable of both independent projects and collaborative teamwork. Pretty good in **UI/UX** design using programs like **Photoshop** and **Figma**.

EDUCATION

Elementary school	Sep 2010 - Jul 2018
LIGITICITUM Y SCHOOL	360 2010 301 2010

't Startblok, Eindhoven

VMBO-T Sep 2018 - Jul 2022

Sint Joris college, Eindhoven

Software Development Sep 2022 - Present

SintLucas, Eindhoven

EMPLOYMENT

Shelf stacker May 2019 - Jun 2020

Jumbo, Eindhoven

Bartender/Waiter Aug 2021 - Present

Brasserie Ludiek, Veldhoven